不 谢谢
No, thanks.
如果我想看照片，我会去照片冲洗店
If I want to look at pictures,I go to Fotomat.
此外，罗斯把我带来了
Besides, Rose brought me.
她带着狗在外面等着
She's waiting outside with the dog.
嘿  你有没有在时速50英里的时候把头伸出车窗外
Hey, you ever stick your head out of a car window doing 50?
冲得好快啊！
What a rush.
朋友
Friend?
哈喽？
Hello?
你想要什么？
What do you want?
她又来了
She's here again.
她在看着我
She was watching me.
赶紧去你床上睡觉
Try and get back to sleep
伯金医生要是看见你在我床上就糟了
before Dr. Birkin finds you in my bed.
我看见她了
I saw her.
你没有...
You didn't...
你什么都没看到
You didn't see anything.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
你是什么，变态吗
What are you, a pervert?
我结婚45年了
I was married for 45 years,
我连我丈夫珍藏的名画都没见过
I never even saw my husband's Gauguins.
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
丽莎·特雷弗？
Lisa Trevor?
你住在这里吗？
Do you live here?
你住在哪里？
Where do you live?
下面吗？
Below?
嘿
Hey.
你下床干什么，小姑娘
What are you doing out of bed, little girl?
嗯?
Well?
自从父母去世后，她有时会梦游
She sleepwalks sometimes since our parents died.
哦
Oh.
那么
Well, then.
去睡觉吧，你们两个
Off to bed, both of you.
等等
Wait.
雷德菲尔德，是吗？
Redfield, isn't it?
克里斯和克莱尔    雷德菲尔德？
Chris and Claire Redfield?
你这么照顾你妹妹，真是个好孩子
You're a good boy for taking such care of your sister.
晚安
Good night.
那一定是个静静的梦
That must have been quite some dream.
我差点就被吓屎了
I almost shit my goddamn pants.
如果我知道你会在做梦时尖叫
If I knew you were gonna be screaming in your sleep,
我会把你丢在路边的
I would've left you at the side of the road.
1998年9月30日
你搭便车出门干什么？
What are you doing out hitchhiking
而且还是这样的夜晚？
on a night like this anyway?
哦 耶
Oh, yeah.
去看你哥哥，你说的
Going to see your brother, you said.
对
Right.
你说以前住在这里
Used to live here, you said.
浣熊市
Raccoon City.
你比我好
Better you than me.
你知道的，回到那个鬼地方
You know, one might have nightmares
可能会让你噩梦连连
heading back into that shithole town.
自从保护伞离开后，
Nothing left 'cept the raccoons
除了浣熊什么都没留下
since Umbrella started to leave.
你介意吗
Do you mind?
他们应该告诉你哥哥
They should tell your brother,
“赶紧离开那里”
"Just get out of there."
“收拾东西走人吧“
"Just pack up and leave."
不过，你要把房子卖给谁
Although, who you gonna sell your house to?
没有谁  那是谁
Nobody. That's who.
住在浣熊市
Live in Raccoon?
不,谢谢 不可能
No, thanks. No way.
也许你想一直坐到加特林
Maybe you want to stay on till Gatlin,
告诉他你改变了主意
tell him you had a change of heart.
不管怎么说，人们太重视家庭了
People put too much emphasis on family anyway.
有时候你就得放手
Sometimes you just got to let it go.
小心
Watch out!
糟了
Shit!
她...
Is she...
哦   不不不不不不
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
操
Fuck!
我没--我都没看见她   她不知从哪冒出来
I di-- I didn't see her. She came out of nowhere.
她半夜在外面干什么？
What's she doing out here in the middle of the night?
我们得找点东西把尸体包起来
We need something to wrap the body in.
你也看到了，对吧?  这不是我的错
You saw it, right? It wasn't my fault.
天哪   我 操
Jesus. Oh, fuck!
操   听我说
Fuck!Listen to me.
我们得找点东西把尸体包起来
We need something to wrap the body in,
然后把它带到城里去
and then we're gonna take it into town.
这不是我的错
It wasn't my fault!
哦  天哪   我操
Oh, Jesus! Fuck!
我哥哥是警察  他能帮助我们
My brother's a cop. He can help us.
警察
Cop?
但这不是我的错    不是我的错
But it's not my fault. It's not my fault!
我知道   我知道
I know. I know.
我操 我操
Fuck! Fuck!
我们不能把她留在这里，明白吗
We can't just leave her here, okay?
我操
Fuck.
我操  我操  我操  我操
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
她去哪了？
Where the fuck did she go?
哈喽
Hello?
嘿
Hey!
你出了车祸
You've been in an accident,
你需要帮助
and you need help.
我们得跟着她
We need to go after her.
你他妈的想干什么就干什么去吧
You can do whatever the fuck you want.
我他妈的要离开这里
I'm getting the fuck out of here.
生化危机
浣熊市，这里曾经是 世界上最大的制药公司"保护伞公司"的总部，现在却成了一座鬼城。保护伞公司正在搬迁到一个新的地方。剩下的只有最后几名骨干员工...还有那些太穷而无法离开的人
我操
Fuck.
哦  我操
Oh, fuck.
嘿，你为什么不坐下来呢
Hey, why don't you just take a seat
让那可怜的孩子一个人呆着吧，威斯克？
and leave the poor kid alone, huh, Wesker?
OK
十块钱
Ten bucks.
我赌十块钱，你射不中那个
Ten bucks says you can't shoot that off from here.
这很简单
That's easy.
你疯了吗
Jesus fucking Christ.
用这个，瓦伦蒂安
With this, Valentine.
我操，这是啥？
I mean, what the fuck?
20块，我连看都不用看 就可以打掉瓶子
我是说，当然，你的钱我赢定了
I mean, yeah, sure, I'll take your money.
什么鬼？
What the fuck?
我操
Fuck.
嘿!  你打盹了，你输了
Hey!You snooze, you lose.
等等
Wait...
现在是吉尔的三明治了
It's Jill's sandwich now.
快点
Come on.
给钱
Pay up.
快点  给钱
Come on. Pay up.
伙计们
Fellas.
你在后面吗，路易丝？
You back there, Louise?
哈喽 伙计们
Hello, boys.
您要点什么
What can I get you?
两杯咖啡 外带
Two coffees to go.
漫长的一天
Long day?
-嗨,我可以…        -哦，你一定是…
-Hey, could I...    -Oh, you must be...
那个菜鸟
the rookie.
怎么样，菜鸟？
How you doing, rookie?
那个   我听说
So, I heard
你在训练时射中了你搭档的屁股
that you shot your partner in the ass during training.
是真的吗？
Is that true?
还有你的，呃，
And that your, uh,
爸爸，警队的某个大人物，
daddy, some big shot on the force,
不得不把你保释出来
that he had to bail you out.
这就是为什么他们把你调到这个
Now, is that why they transferred you to this...
狗屎小镇？
shithole town?
对      里昂S 肯尼迪
Yeah.Leon S. Kennedy.
“S”代表什么?“愚蠢”吗
What's the "S" stand for? "Stupid"?
别这样，我们只是在逗你玩，小子
Come on, we're just playing with you, kiddo.
你们都在墓地工作吗？
Y'all working the graveyard?
是的  你们要去哪里？
Yep. Where you guys headed?
嗯，有人发现了一具尸体
Well, someone found a body
在斯宾塞旧宅邸——都被咬烂了
up at the old Spencer Mansion-- it's all chewed up.
我以为那儿已经没有东西了
Didn't think there was anything up there anymore.
就我而言他们越早关闭整个镇子越好
Well, the sooner they shut this whole town down, the better,as far as I'm concerned
嘿,嘿
Hey, hey.
你们说的是我的家乡
It's my hometown you're talking about.
好吧，欢迎光临
Well, you're welcome to it.
嘿, 来吧    我们得赶快行动了
Hey, come on. We got to shake a leg.
还有  别开枪
And don't shoot.
我投降
I'm unarmed.
操  这家伙
Fuck that guy.
好了  那么   呃
Right, so, uh...
我想我得给钱了？
I guess I'm paying?
快点，我们该去警局了
Come on, we should get to the station.
嘿    不要在意我们
Hey. Pay us no mind.
一旦你了解我们，你就会发现我们是好人
We're, uh, nice people once you get to know us.
我是吉尔·瓦伦蒂安
I'm Jill Valentine.
里昂    肯尼迪
Leon... Kennedy.
很高兴认识你  里昂肯尼迪
Nice to meet you, Leon Kennedy.
你没机会的
I wouldn't go there.
她眼里只有那个大块头
She's only got eyes for the big fella,
我不认为你能打败他
and I don't fancy your chances against him.
你真的射中了自己的搭档吗？
You really shoot your own partner?
是 是的
Y-Yeah.
嗯，说来话长
Um, it's a long story.
你
You...
你的眼睛怎么了
What's going on with your eye?
哦
Oh.
我不知道，过去几周它一直这样
I don't know, it's been doing that the last couple of weeks.
你难道不想去看下医生吗？
You don't think you should see someone about that?
不
Yeah.
没什么大不了的
It's probably nothing.
嘿，那个，呃   那个女人
Hey, that, uh... that woman...
可能并不像看上去那么糟糕，对吧？
That probably just wasn't as bad as it seemed, right?
是的 当然
Yeah. Sure.
谢谢你让我搭车
Thanks for the ride.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
你怎么了？
What's going on with you?
别对我发火，你这狗娘养的
Don't go getting ill on me, you son of a bitch.
我没有给你买保险
I don't have insurance for you.
啊!   我操
Aah! Fuck!
你他妈的敢咬我，你这个狗娘养的！
You fucking bit me, you motherfucker!
我操
Fuck!
看来  你还在想念吉尔
Still pining after Jill, I see.
不可能的，兄弟
Never gonna happen, bro.
他对我就像父亲一样
He's been like a father to me.
我看见你在给胸部打蜡
I see you wax your chest now.
别笑
Funny.
自从你逃跑后
After you ran away,
威廉就是我最亲的人了
William was the closest thing I had to family.
你怎么进来的
How'd you get in?
撬了你的锁
Picked your lock.
你知道我是个警察吧？
You realize I'm a cop, right?
你的安全措施得改进一下
You need better security.
这是一个普通的锁，克莱尔
It's a single-cylinder dead bolt, Claire.
多数人都会先敲门的
Most people knock.
是的, 我敲过了
Yeah, I tried.
没人应答
No one answered.
所以你才撬
So you broke in.
你为什么回来？
Why are you back here?
太想念浣熊市了？还特地来找我？
Missed Raccoon City so much you had to come pay me a visit?
是的
Yeah.
我他妈的爱死浣熊市了
I fucking love Raccoon City.
“加油，强盗们”
"Go, you Bandits."
你这混蛋
You're an asshole.
不，你知道吗？
No, you know what?
我欠这个小镇的…我欠柏金医生和保护伞公司的一切
I owe this town... I owe Birkin and Umbrella everything.
他们养育了我，让我进入学校，进大学
They raised me, put me through school, the academy.
他们在那里等我
They were there for me.
你在哪里？
Where were you?
你都五年没联系过我了
I haven't even heard from you in five years.
很高兴见到你
Nice seeing you.
克里斯，等等
Chris, wait.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我现在回来了
I'm back now.
听着     我觉得这个地方
Look... I think there's something
可能就要发生点什么事
seriously wrong with this place.
你是什么意思?   好吧      我
What do you mean?Okay, so I-I was
我当时在搭便车，然后…
hitching a ride in a truck, and...
拦路搭车 --   也是违法的
Soliciting a ride-- also illegal.
那逮捕我
Arrest me.
听着，我们撞了个人
Look, we kind of hit this person,
但  但他们就这么站起来，然后就 就直接走了
but-but they just got up and they-they walked away.
你撞了个人   天啊,  克莱尔
You hit someone? Holy shit, Claire.
你报警了吗?
Have you reported it?
我这不正在报警吗
I'm reporting it now.
你难道没在听我说话？
You not listening to me?
他们 他们站起来就 就走了
They-they just got up and-and walked off.
你可能变成了肇事逃逸的一方
You could be party to a hit-and-run.
嘘   听着
Shush. Just...
不，克莱尔，我没有时间处理这个
No, Claire, I don't have time for this.
不，听着，好吧，我一直
No. Look, okay, so I've been talking
在聊天室和这个家伙聊天
to this guy in a chat room...
聊天室是什么鬼地方？
What the fuck's a chat room?
就是人们在网上聊天的地方
It's a place on the Internet where people chat.
行了   自己看吧
Just... just watch it.
他叫本·贝托鲁奇
His name's Ben Bertolucci.
它在水里，克莱尔
It's in the water, Claire.
它就在该死的在水里
It's in the fucking water.
嗯  整个镇子都被毒害了
Um, this whole town's been poisoned.
慢慢地，年复一年
Slowly, over years and years,
然后  呃   人们开始生病
and, uh, people are getting sick.
哦  拜托    克莱尔
Oh, come on, Claire.
又来了  嘘
Not again.Shh!
你  嘘        瞧  呃
You "shh."See, uh,
保护伞公司认为他们可以  呃
Umbrella just thought that they could, uh,
收拾行李走人     任由城镇腐烂
pack up shop and let this town rot away
然后离开，重新开始
while they go off and-and start afresh
然后在别的地方摇身一变，然后
somewhere else all shiny and-and new, and...
他们差点儿就这么做了，但   呃
they almost fucking did it, but, uh,
几天前，他们发生了一个小事故
a couple days ago, they had a little incident.
我说的不仅仅是污染水源的废物
And I'm not just talking about waste poisoning the water.
不，我说的是严重的泄露
No, I'm talking about a real bad leak.
就像切尔诺贝利，你懂我的意思吧
Like Chernobyl, if you know what I mean.
然后 呃  他们一直在试图控制这一切
And, uh, they've been trying to contain that shit,
但现在妖怪已经从瓶子里出来了
but the genie is out of the bottle now,
而我… 我觉得它不会再进去了
and I... I don't think it's going back in.
我害怕,   克莱尔  我 …
I'm afraid, Claire. I'm a...
我害怕他们会毁了这个小镇 …
I'm afraid of what they're gonna do to this town...
而且小镇里还有人
and the people in it.
从那以后，我再也没能和他联系上了
I've not been able to make contact with him since.
好
Great.
他疯了，可能还很危险
He's crazy and probably dangerous.
听着，你的阴谋论 在我们小的时候 就不是真的
Look, your conspiracy theories weren't true when we were kids.
现在 他们也不是真的
They're not true now.
好吧?       你到底来这里干什么？
All right? Why are you really here?
你失业了吗?   您需要钱吗?
Did you lose your job? Do you need cash?
你突然出现在这里，闯进我的房子
You show up here, you break into my house.
什么   什么样的人会这样开锁啊？
What-what kind of person can pick a lock like that?
这 这真让人受不了，而且   这是什么鬼？
It-it's kind of impressive, but also, what the fuck?
对不起，我得准备去上班了
I'm sorry, I got to get ready for work.
克里斯
Chris.
我操
Fuck.
亲爱的,嘿   妈妈和爸爸在这里
Honey, hey. Mom and Dad are here.
我看到了一个怪物
I saw a monster.
哦  亲爱的，你刚才只是做了个噩梦
Oh, honey, you just had a bad dream.
嘘  但 但 但我确实看到他了
Shh.But-but... but I did see him.
他浑身青一块紫一块的
He was all green and slimy,
他有黄色的大眼睛和牙齿，像这样
and he had big yellow eyes and teeth, like this.
我想我也会害怕的 对吧，亲爱的？
I think I'd be frightened, too. Right, honey?
哦，我的天哪，我会被吓呆的
Oh, my gosh, I'd be petrified.
真可怕
Terrified.
好了，没事的
Come on. It's okay.
我不会让任何东西伤害你的
I'd never let anything hurt you.
我马上回来，好吗？
I'll be right back, okay?
好了，让我们来
All right, let's get you
睡觉觉吧，好吗         但   但  等等
back to sleep, okay?  But-but wait.
-如果怪物回来怎么办？     - 哈喽
-What if the monster comes back?   -Hello?
亲爱的，世上没有怪物，好吗？
Honey, there's no such thing as monsters, okay?
- 你保证吗        - 我保证
- Do you promise? - I promise.
...真是好主意
...really good thoughts.
那我们就这么做，好吗？
So let's do that, okay?
还记得上次我们去游泳吗
Remember last time we went swimming.
好吗？想一想
All right? Think about that.
我们得走了
We need to go.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
-打电话的是谁?                -马上
-Who was on the telephone?  -Now!
发生什么事了，威廉
What is happening, William?
给雪莉穿好衣服，在车里等我
Get Sherry dressed and meet me at the car.
呃   好的
Uh, okay.
呃   嘿，看着我   看着我
Uh, hey, look at me. Look at me.
这里是保护伞公司
This is the Umbrella Corporation.
为了你们的安全，请呆在家里
For your safety, please stay in your homes
等待进一步指示
and await further instructions.
这里是保护伞公司
This is the Umbrella Corporation.
为了你们的安全，请呆在家里
For your safety, please stay in your homes
等待进一步指示
and await further instructions.
这里是保护伞公司
This is the Umbrella Corporation.
那是什么？
What is that?
为了你们的安全，请呆在家里
For your safety, please stay in your homes
等待进一步指示
and await further instructions.
没什么， 那没什么
Nothing. It's nothing.
我得去趟警局   给你  钱不是很多
I got to get to the station. Here. It's not much.
拿着吧，好吗？
Just take it, okay?
如果你要离开的话 ，请锁好门
Lock-pick the door behind you when you leave.
克里斯 克里斯
Chris. Chris!
离开这里，好吗？
Just get out of here, okay?
这里是保护伞公司
This is the Umbrella Corporation.
为了你们的安全... 不要碰我的摩托车！
For your safety... And don't touch the bike!
... 等待进一步指示
...and await further instructions.
这里是保护伞公司
This is the Umbrella Corporation.
为了你们的安全， 请呆在家里
For your safety, please stay in your homes
等待进一步指示
and await further instructions.
这里是保护伞公司
This is the Umbrella Corporation.
你怎么没生病？   大哥
Why aren't you sick, big brother?
需要帮忙吗
Can I help you?
哈喽
Hello?
嘿   你需要帮助吗？
Hey. You need help?
是你需要帮助
You need help.
什么？
What?
哦  糟糕
Oh, shit!
这里是保护伞公司
This is the Umbrella Corporation.
为了你们的安全， 请呆在家里
For your safety, please stay in your homes
等待进一步指示
and await further instructions.
这里是保护伞公司
This is the Umbrella Corporation.
为了你们的安全， 请呆在家里
For your safety, please stay in your homes
等待进一步指示
and await further instructions.
最糟糕的死亡方式是什么？
What would the worst way to die be?
什么？
What?
被蛇整个吞下
To be swallowed whole by a snake
还是被大白鲨活活吃掉？
or eaten alive by a great white shark?
你是个怪胎，瓦朗蒂安
You're a freak, Valentine.
我打算在床上安详地死去
I plan on dying peacefully in bed,
依偎在威斯克粗壮的臂膀里
snuggled in Wesker's big burly arms.
我也是，兄弟
Me, too, brother.
有趣
Funny.
维克斯在这里干什么？
Uh, what's Vickers doing here?
我们以为直升机丢了
Thought we lost the chopper
预算也削减了
with the rest of the budget cuts.
也许他只是想我们了
Maybe he just missed us.Oh.
去你的
Fuck you.
是这样吗？
Is that right?
我想不是
Guess not
嘿
Hey!
好了，警长，这是怎么回事？
Okay, Chief, what's this all about?
是啊，警报器怎么了？
Yeah, what's with the alarm?
停电了   好吧，如果你们都能
Power's out . Well, if you all
消停几分钟听我说
shut the hell up for a second and listen,
也许你们会搞清楚的
maybe you'll find out.
-老实说，我不知道         -你不知道？
-Honestly, I don't know.   -You don't know?
没错，雷德菲尔德   我不知道
That's right, Redfield. I do not know.
我只知道马里尼和杜利
What I do know is that Marini and Dooley
现在没有回应他们的广播
are currently not answering their radios.
他们在调查斯宾塞大厦附近的一具尸体
They're investigating a report of a body up by the Spencer Mansion.
你觉得有联系吗？
You think it's connected?
呃   斯宾塞大厦是什么？
Um, what's the Spencer Mansion?
嗯，我想你们大多数人都知道
Well, as I think most of you know,
奥斯瓦尔德·斯宾塞是保护伞公司的创始人
Oswald Spencer was the creator of the Umbrella Corporation,
而这座大厦就是他的家
and the mansion was his home
直到那一年他去世...
until the year of his death in...
你他妈的在这里干什么？里昂
What the fuck are you doing here, Leon?!
天啊
Holy shit.
你说过“大家都到简报室去”
You said, "Everyone into the briefing room,"
所以 我 我来了
so I... here I am.
我不是说你，你这个白痴
I didn't mean you, you moron.
没叫你，里昂  是其他人
Not you, Leon. Everyone else.
如果有人进来，而前台接待处
What if someone wanders in and there's
没有人怎么办？
no one behind the front desk?
比如一个老太太在找她的猫之类的
An old lady's looking for her cat or something
-是，你说得对     - 耶稣了个基督
-Yeah, you're right.  -Jesus Christ
-快回到那儿去，伙计         - 你说得对 可以
-Get back there, man.      -You're right. Okay.
然后去理个发，你这个该死的嬉皮士
And get a haircut, you goddamn hippie.
天啊
Geez.
不是伍德斯托克
It's not Woodstock.
噢，放松点，警长
Aw, take it easy on the rook, Chief.
对 对不起，威斯克    这重要吗？
I-I'm sorry, Wesker. Is that important?
-不  那个    我  我很好        - 新女友吗？
-No, it's-it's... I'm-I'm good.  -A new girlfriend?
哈？
Huh?
也许你可以带她去好莱坞星球吃饭
Maybe you could take her out to eat at Planet Hollywood.
他们在加特林有一个新的
They have a new one in Gatlin.
哦，他们有很好吃的沙拉
Oh, they got a great salad.
和小酒
Little wine.
或者干脆把她带回你的公寓
Or maybe just take her back to your apartment,
在百视达租一部电影，舒服地躺在沙发上
rent a movie at Blockbuster, get cozy on the couch,
或者玩《风之旅人》游戏
or put on some Journey.
史蒂夫·佩里的声音，对女人的心有什么影响？哈
Steve Perry's voice, what it does to a woman's heart, huh?
我说得对吗？
Am I right?
听起来怎么样？
How's that sound?
听起来我可能要上床了
Sounds like I might be getting laid.
但今晚不会发生了
But it ain't gonna happen tonight,
因为我要你们五分钟后穿好衣服，所有人
because I want you dressed in five, all of you,
准备起飞，因为我想知道
and ready to fly, because I want to know
B队在哪里
where the hell Bravo team is
还有那些该死的警报器是干嘛的
and what the fuck all those alarms are about!
你们明白吗?   快点，动起来   走
You got me? Come on, get moving. Go.
动作快点
Get a move on it!
嘿 我们在直升机上见
Hey, I'll meet you guys in the chopper.
这他妈是什么东西？
What the fuck is this?
你所需要知道的一切都在这个设备上
浣熊市将在上午6点被摧毁
威斯克，我们走吧
Wesker, let's get going.
慢一点   威廉
Slow down, William.
你 你会撞车的
Y-You're gonna crash.
威廉，慢点！
William, slow down!
我们要去哪里？
Where are we going?
你为什么不能告诉我     为什么我们要这么急着离开？
Why can't you tell me why we're in such a hurry to leave?
离开           这就是他们想要的
Leaving-- that's what they want.
所以他们可以毁掉我一生的工作
So they can destroy my life's work.
爸爸，小心！
Daddy, watch out!
你差点撞到那个女孩
You almost hit that girl.
你还好吗
You okay?
醒醒
Wake up.
我们需要你赶紧起来     然后和我们一起走
We need you to get up and come with us.
我们要去哪里？嘘
Where are we going?Shh.
没事的，小女孩
It's okay, little girl.
因为我们给你找了一个新家庭
Because we have found you a new family.
他们就在外面等你
They're waiting for you just outside.
这一切都非常令人兴奋
It's all so very exciting.
哦，别担心你哥哥
Oh, don't worry about your brother.
到时候他也会来的
He'll be coming along as well, in due course.
我们永远不会把你们俩分开的
We would never separate the two of you.
我们只要你 跟着我们走
We just need you to come with us,
然后 有人会帮你收拾东西的
and someone will collect all of your belongings.
威廉
William!
凌晨1点
什么鬼
What the fuck?
你可能需要一个灭火器
You might want to get a fire extinguisher.
然后锁上大门   可能还有其他的
And lock the gates. There may be others.
啊？ 其他... 其他的什么？
Huh? Oth... Other what?
去他妈的
Fuck this.
嗨  嗯，长官，嗯
Hi. Uh, sir, um...
-呃，发生什么事了？”    -因为，嗯
-Uh, what's going on?   -'Cause, um...
我们应该...  我们应该呼叫吗？
Should we... should we call someone?
你要呼叫谁？你就是警察啊
Who you gonna call? You're the police.
救护车？
An ambulance?
听着，我不是医学专家
Look, I'm no medical expert,
但我觉得那家伙可能没救了
but I think that guy might just be beyond saving,
此外，我想你已经发现
Besides, I think you'll find
城里所有的电话线都断了
that all the phone lines in the city are dead.
照顾好自己吧   里昂
Take care of yourself, Leon.
我操  我操
Fuck. Fuck.
呃  长官 嘿 嘿
Uh, sir? Hey, hey.
长官
Sir!
你要  你要去哪里？  长官
Where-where are you going, sir?
嘿  长官   呃 我知道我是新来的
Hey, sir, um, I know I'm new here
我真的不知道发生了什么，但是，嗯
and I don't really know what's going on, but, um...
那么，你要去哪里？
so, where are you going?
现在谁负责？
Who's in charge now?
- 是你       -呃，不，不，不
- You are. -Uh, no, no, no.
不 呃    我 我是个新手，对吧？
No, um, I'm-I'm a rookie, right?
是啊，那么 恭喜你，菜鸟，关于升职
Yeah, well, congratulations, rookie, on the promotion.
我相信你父亲会非常自豪的
I'm sure your father would be incredibly proud
为他那可怜的儿子
that his pathetic specimen of a son
升职得如此之快
is rising so quickly through the ranks.
长 长官，我真的觉得你不该去
S-Sir, I-I really don't think you should go.
我  我觉得我还没准备好…
I-I don't think I'm prepared to handle...
我要走了  稍息  保重  祝你好运
I'm going. At ease. Take care. Good luck.
我知道你会做得很好的
I know you'll do a great job.
长官
Sir.
Sir!
我操
Fuck.
就在这里.
Right here.
无线电呼叫    告诉他我们找到b队的吉普车了
Radio Irons. Tell him we found Bravo team's Jeep.
好的
Will do.
天啊
Holy shit.
耶稣了个基督   这里到底发生了什么？
Jesus Christ. What the hell happened here?
他们在哪里？
Where are they?
这他妈的怎么了？
What the fuck is wrong with it?
真的吗
Really?
什么
What?
应该没收你的枪的
Someone should confiscate that.
嘿，伙计们
Just...Uh, hey, guys?
他们往这边走了
They went this way.
马里尼和杜利就在这里
Marini and Dooley are in here somewhere.
我们应该分头行动
We should split up.
什么
What?
我们越快找到他们
The faster we find them,
就能越快离开这个鬼地方
the faster we can get the fuck out of here.
好了，我们两人一组
All right, we go in pairs.
我和你一起去，威斯克
I'll go with you, Wesker.
你们要时刻保持警惕
Keep your shit wired at all times.
这可不好
This is not good.
这里是保护伞公司
This is the Umbrella Corporation.
返回你的交通工具
Return to your vehicles,
然后返回你的住所和公司
and return to your homes and businesses.
拜托，后退
Come on! Go back!
后退  把你的卡车倒回去！
Go back! Move your truck back!
我们被封锁了！
We're blocked in!
还要多久？
How much longer is this gonna be?
哦   该死的   哦
Oh, goddamn it. Oh!
哦  该死  该死  该死  该死
Oh, damn, damn, damn, damn.
开门！拜托，求你了！
Open up! Come on, please!
滚开   该死的 离我的车远点！
Get off! Get the fuck away from my car!
滚开   杰克  滚开
Get off, Jack! Get off!
请不要开枪 我没有武器
Please don't shoot. I'm unarmed.
操   哦  该死的
Fuck! Oh, goddamn!
哦  天哪
Oh, man!
哦  就差一点
Oh, that is close.
哦  操
Oh, shit.
浣熊市，已经封锁戒严
Raccoon City, locked down and secured.
请让我进去吧
Please let me in.
让我进去
Let me in.
凌晨1：50
快点  快点
Come on, come on.
该死的子弹
Goddamn bullets.
嘿 嘿    扔掉你的枪!  举起手来
Hey, hey! Drop your gun! Show me your hands!
我没有枪
Haven't got a gun.
你他妈的是谁？
Who the fuck are you?
快点
Come on.
里昂，把枪放下
Leon, put that gun down.
那么，又到你说了算吗？
So, are you in charge again?
请让我进去
Please let me in.
让我进去
Let me in!
Let... me in.
我哥哥克里斯·雷德菲尔德在哪里？
Where's my brother, Chris Redfield?
那么 你是克里斯的妹妹，是吗？
So you're Chris's little sister, huh?
我以为你们俩没说过话
I didn't think the two of you spoke.
他在阿尔克雷山上
He's up in the Arklay Mountains
-和A队的其他人一起     --嘿  呃 对不起
-with the rest of Alpha team. --Hey, um, sorry.
有没有人想告诉我 这到底是怎么回事吗？
Does someone want to tell me what the fuck is going on here?
我是说，他们怎么了？
I mean, what's happening to them?
很明显，糟透了
Clearly, some bad shit.
浣熊市的所有出口都被保护伞公司封锁了
All the exits out of Raccoon have been blocked by Umbrella.
我们需要更多的弹药和枪支
We need more ammo and guns.
军械库在楼下 你要去哪里？
The armory's downstairs.Where are you going?
我会设法找到你哥哥的
I'm gonna try and get ahold of your brother.
浣熊市已经无路可走了
There's no way out of Raccoon by road,
但我们也许可以坐直升机
but we might just be able to take a helicopter.
凌晨2：00
那是什么
What is that?
嗯，我稍后再给你解释
Uh, I'll explain in a minute.
嘿 警察局
Hey. RPD.
救我
Help me.
举手，让我看看你的手
Hands. Show me your hands.
什么鬼
What the fuck?
我命令你呆在那里
I need you to stay right there.
哦   我操
Oh, fuck.
马里尼  操
Marini. Fuck.
好的  这里  这里  这里  这里  这里
Okay, here, here, here, here, here.
这个  压住这里   是吗
It's... Put pressure right there, okay?
尽可能压住这里
As much pressure as you can.
去找杜利
Find Dooley.
你会没事的，好吗
You're gonna be okay, all right?
你会没事的   这没什么
You'll be fine. It's just nothing.
坚持住，伙计，好吗
Just hold on, man, all right? It's...
操   不不不不
Shit. No, no, no, no.
杜利
Dooley.
理查德
Richard!
雷德菲尔德
Redfield!
艾肯
Aiken!
快他妈的离开这里
Let's get the fuck out of here!
你他妈的在干什么，威斯克？等等
The fuck you doing, Wesker?Hold on.
听着   你听到了吗？
Listen. Do you hear that?
维克斯到底在干什么？
What the hell is Vickers doing?
快跑
Run!
凌晨2：29
是的，实际上我从来没有进过这个房间，所以，嗯
Yeah, I've actually never been in this room, so, um...
好东西，对吧？
That's good, right?
我想那只是
I think it's just, uh...
-我觉得有点卡住了     -给我
-Think it's sort of jammed.  -Here. Uh...
穿上这个
Put this on.
那么，你怎么知道这么多关于枪的事？
So, how do you know so much about guns?
我八岁时父母死于车祸
My parents died in a car accident when I was eight.
我和哥哥在这里的孤儿院长大
My brother and I grew up in an orphanage here.
我很久以前就逃跑了
I ran away a long time ago.
我必须快点学会保护自己
I had to learn to handle myself quickly.
是啊
Right. Yeah.
你可能想知道像我这样的人当警察
You're probably wondering what a guy like me
是为了什么，对吧
is doing as a cop, right?
有点
Kinda.
是啊 我也是
Yeah. Me, too.
嘿   来人 救我出去！
Hey! Someone get me out of here!
-哈喽     -你是警察 你去
-Hello?  -Your police station.
我看看还能找到什么
I'll see what else I can find.
我在该死的地下室
I'm in the fucking basement.
他们把我关在该死的地下室
They put me in the fucking basement.
把我弄出去
Get me out of here.
我知道你在上面
I know you're up there.
哦，感谢上帝
Oh, thank God.
感谢该死的上帝
Thank fucking God.
你得把我弄出去，伙计
You got to get me out of here, man.
你他妈的是谁？
Who the fuck are you?
等你把我弄出去后 我再告诉你 怎么样？
How about I tell you once you get me the fuck out of here?
天哪
Jesus.
他没事吧
Is he okay?
他
Him?
哦，是的，不，他很好
Oh, yeah, no, he's fucking fine. Yeah.
是的   当你生病时  地板上咳点血
Yeah, who doesn't cough up a little blood on the floor
是很正常的
when they're feeling sick?
只是有点冷
Just a little cold.
当然了 他一点不都好了，伙计
Of course he's not fucking okay, man.
看看他       打开那该死的门
Look at him. Open the goddamn door.
你 你为什么被关起来？
Why-why are you locked up?
为什么
Why?
因为我发现了真相
Because I found out the truth.
真相？ 什么 什么真相？
The truth? What-what truth?
听我说，你这该死的男孩乐队粉丝
Listen to me, you fucking boy band wannabe.
你认为保护伞公司会把所有的时间
You think Umbrella spend all their time
都花在制造阿司匹林和维生素片上吗？
making aspirins and little vitamin tablets?
-不可能的        -耶稣了个基督
-No fucking way.  -Jesus Christ.
-打开那该死的门    - 那是我的枪
-Open the goddamn door.  -That's my gun.
-快点    -你没必要这么做
-Do it.   -You don't have to do this.
当然，没必要
Sure, I don't.
你 和你所有的警察朋友
And you and all your police buddies,
你们不像镇上的其他人一样生病
you're not sick like the rest of the town
只是因为你们有良好的免疫系统 对吧
just 'cause you got a good immune system, right?
妈的，你可能打了一针
Fuck, you probably had a little injection,
一片你都没意识到的维生素片
a little vitamin pill you didn't even realize.
让你们安全至少一段时间
Keeps you safe at least for a while.
但是其他人，那些普通人
But the others, ordinary people,
那些牺牲品
expendable ones...
真他妈的走运，对吧？
Yeah, good fucking luck, right?
打开那该死的门
Open the goddamn door.
钥匙在那边桌子里
The keys are over there in the desk.
快点
Do it!
知道了
Here I go.
耶稣
Jesus...
了个基督
fucking Christ.
快点  伙计  耶稣了个基督
Come on, man. Jesus fucking Christ.
赶快
Hurry up.
哦  我操
Oh, fuck me.
你听说过T病毒和G病毒吗？
Yeah, you ever heard of the T-Virus and the G-Virus?
当然了，他妈的当然没有听说过
Uh, of course you fucking haven't.
这是一种能改变活细胞DNA基因的病毒
Well, it's a virus that genetically modifies the DNA of a living cell,
它把这些人变成了该死的武器，伙计
and it's turning these people into fucking weapons, man.
你得把我从这里弄出来，好吗
You need to get me the fuck out of here, okay?
这事别太认真
Be an asshole about it.
是的，我已经抓住机会了
Yeah, well, I'm done taking chances.
快点，伙计 耶稣了个基督
Come on, man. Jesus fucking Christ.
好了  你知道什么？ 请等一下
All right. You know what? Just one second, please.
你不是爱因斯坦，不是吗，伙计？
You're no Einstein, are you, buddy?
感谢该死的上帝
Thank fucking God.
本
Ben.
振作起来
Get your shit together,
否则你会熬不过去的
or you're not gonna make it through the night.
你完事了吗？
Are you done?
我真的很想离开这个小镇
I just really want to get out of this town.
维克斯，收到了吗？完毕
Vickers, can you read me? Over.
维克斯，我是铁人队长
Vickers, this is Chief Irons.
拿起你那该死的对讲机
Pick up your damn radio!
维克斯，收到了吗？
Vickers, can you read me?
完毕
Over
维克斯  我是铁人队长   拿起你那该死的对讲机
Vickers, this is Irons. Pick up your damn radio.
你救了我的命
You saved my life.
拜托
Come on.
拜托  拜托
Come on, come on.
天哪  她说的是真的
Holy shit, she was telling the truth.
真的   什么是真的？
Truth about what?
威斯克，怎么了？
Wesker, what's going on?
他们几个月前联系过我
They contacted me several months ago.
曾经有一次，保护伞公司开始将他们的业务移出浣熊市
It was once Umbrella started moving their operations out of Raccoon.
我不知道他们是谁
I don't know who they are.
我不知道，我也不在乎
I don't know, and I don't care.
他们只是一些既得利益者
They're just some people with a vested interest
他们有着大量肮脏的秘密
in getting hold of whatever dirty secrets
保护伞公司把它们存放在在地下 然后就泄露了
Umbrella are keeping down there and exposing them.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
拜托，吉尔  别那样看着我
Come on, Jill. Don't look at me like that.
不就是钱吗
It's just money.
好吧   他们还有很多
All right? And they have plenty of it.
这只是逃离小镇死胡同生活的一种方式
It was just a way of getting out of this small-town, dead-end life.
所以
So, uh...
...你打算离开我们
...you were just gonna leave us?
拜托
Come on.
我们得找到克里斯和理查德
We have to find Chris and Richard
告诉他们维克斯死了
and tell them that Vickers is dead.
拜托
Come on.
拜托   他们是你的朋友
Come on, these are your friends!
我不能
I can't.
哦 天哪
Oh, my God.
这到底是什么状况？
What the fuck happened to him?
我不知道
I don't know.
威斯克
Wesker.
Wesker!
你找到我哥哥了吗？
Did you get ahold of my brother?
没有
No.
我们需要那架直升机离开这里
We need that helicopter to get out of here.
我们需要去阿尔克莱山
We need to get to the Arklay Mountains.
怎么去
How?
我知道一个方法   来吧
I think I know a way. Come on.
装货码头在这边
The loading dock's this way.
凌晨4点
我们在这里干什么？
What are we doing here?
你得起来和我们一起走
We need you to get up and come with us.
我们要去哪里
Where are we going?
我们为什么在这里？
Why are we here?
这个地方有一条秘密通道
This place has a secret passageway
通向斯宾塞大厦
that leads to the Spencer Mansion.
你怎么知道这个地方的？
How'd you know about this place?
他们收买了你，是不是？
They bought you off, didn't they?
他们付钱给你让你对所有的事情保持沉默
They paid you to keep quiet about all the shit
他们在这里干什么
they were doing in here
现在他们让你像我们一样   在这里腐烂
And now they've left you to rot here just like us.
呃 伙计们
Uh, guys?
伙计们
Guys!
不，有个    那有个人
No, there was... there was somebody...
有个人在那里
There was someone there.
-快跑     -快点
-Run!    -Come on!
丽莎·特雷弗
Lisa Trevor.
我们要去斯宾塞大厦
We need to get to the Spencer Mansion.
你知道怎么去的，不是吗？
You know how, don't you?
克莱尔... 克莱尔...
Claire... Claire...
朋友
Friend?
快点
Come on.
我们为什么要进去？
Why are we going in here?
我要我哥哥
I want my brother.
她咬了我的手
She bit my hand.
抓住她
Get her.
第二把钥匙
The second k-k-key.
谢谢你
Thank you.
克莱尔
Claire.
你朋友真奇怪
You got some weird friends.
杜利
Dooley?
我们得去直升机那
We have to get to the helicopter.
威斯克在哪里？
Where's Wesker?
直升机坠毁了 维克斯死了
The helicopter crashed. Vickers is dead.
威斯克背叛了我们，克里斯
Wesker betrayed us, Chris.
什么
What?
他要把我们留在这里等死
He was gonna leave us here to die.
我们必须跟着他，因为我觉得
We have to follow him, 'cause I think
这是我们唯一的出路
it's our only way out of here.
这是什么地方？
What is this place?
那个……保护伞公司在这里做过什么？
What... what were Umbrella doing here?
这是他们从孤儿院把孩子们 带来的地方
This is where they were bringing the kids from the orphanage.
他们对孩子做实验
They were experimenting on 'em.
这就是他们想带我去的地方
This is where they tried to bring me.
克莱尔
Claire.
没关系   不
It's okay. No!
我们去找我哥哥吧
Let's go find my brother.
威廉，你在这下面干什么？
William, what have you been doing down here?
上帝的工作
God's work.
威廉
William
你是怎么...
How did you get d...
不不不不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no.
听着，我来就是为了这个
Listen, I've just come for that.
这是我一生的工作    我不会给任何人的
This is my life's work. I'm not giving it to anybody.
我真的不能给你一个选择，伙计
I'm not really offering you a choice here, pal.
好吧，等等，等等   把...把...把枪放下
Okay, wait, wait. J-Just... just-just put the gun down.
呃，把它放下
Uh, just put it down.
你为谁工作？
Who do you work for?
这不重要
Doesn't matter.
不，我不这么认为
No, I don't suppose it does.
不不不不      爹地
No, no, no, no.Daddy!
小瓶 小瓶
Vials. Vials.
小瓶
Vials.
我需要那个
I need that.
把小瓶递给我
Just hand me the vials.
好吧，别做傻事，女士，好吗？
Okay, don't do anything stupid, lady, okay?
不
No!
我操
Fuck.
那孩子去哪了？孩子
Where'd the kid go? Kid?
孩子
Kid?
什么鬼
What the fuck?
你
You.
你没必要弄成这样
You didn't have to make it like this.
你他妈的在搞什么鬼？
What the hell is wrong with you?
这太操蛋了
This is so fucked.
嘿  没事了
Hey. It's okay.
他杀了他们
He killed them.
天哪 瓦伦蒂安  你那把该死的枪
Jesus, Valentine, you and that fucking gun.
嘿，不，不，不，我们要把你带出去
Hey, no, no, no. We're gonna get you out of here.
不，不，不，吉尔   我搞砸了
No, no, no, Jill. I fucked up.
保护伞会摧毁这个地方
Umbrella are gonna destroy this place.
整个浣熊市    知道吗
All of Raccoon, okay?
这个设施下面有一条火车隧道
There's a train tunnel beneath this facility.
它通向山的另一边，出口是加特林
It leads to the other side of the mountains and into Gatlin.
你得去到火车那
You need to get to that train.
你得马上走   马上
You need to go now.
对不起  伙计
I'm sorry, man.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不会扣动扳机的，孩子
I wouldn't have pulled the trigger, kid.
不不不
No, no, no.
威斯克
Wesker!
快点，这边走
Come on, this over here.
躲好
Hide.
快点  走  走
Come on. Go. Go.
克里斯，出来玩吧
Chris, come out and play.
你真的相信  你能成为我的家人吗
Did you really believe you could be part of my family?
哦，真是个可爱的小兵
Ooh, such a sweet little soldier.
这么忠诚的小家伙
Such a loyal little drone.
你在哪里，克里斯？
Where are you, Chris?
你妹妹这么聪明，而你怎么这么笨？
How could you be so dumb when your sister's so smart?
你知道的
You know...
我差点为杀了你感到难过
I almost feel sad having to kill you.
差点儿
Almost.
你知道的，我应该
You know, I should have taken
带你和你妹妹去实验室的
you and your sister down to the lab.
你可以被做成很好的标本
You would have made excellent specimens.
你   他妈的   离我哥哥    远点
Get... the fuck...away......from my brother.
动手啊
Do it.
克里斯，我的孩子
Chris, my boy.
闭上你的臭嘴
Shut the fuck up.
我很高兴你没事
I'm so glad you're okay.
这真的很好，但我好像断了几根肋骨
This is really nice, but I think I broke some ribs.
哦，天哪
Oh, my God.
-对不起  你疼吗?        -不，不，不
-Sorry. Are you hurt? -No, no, no, no, no, no.
我没事，我没事
I'm fine, I'm fine.
我们得赶紧离开这里
We got to get the fuck out of here.
保护伞会把这里夷为平地的
Umbrella is gonna level this place.
好吧
Okay.
嘿，哇  菜鸟
Hey, whoa. Rookie?
是啊   相信我，我和你一样惊讶，伙计
Yeah. Trust me, I'm as surprised as you are, buddy.
可以走了吗
Shall we go?
走吧
Let's go.
上午5：55
- 我们会启动它的             - 好的
- We'll get it started.   - Okay.
我们只剩下五分钟了
We only have five minutes left
这地方就要自毁了
until the place self-destructs.
它是怎么启动的
How does it all work?
我们就要离开这里了
We're gonna get out of here.
我早就该听你的了
I should've listened to you a long time ago.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没关系
It's okay.
我可能把你摩托车上的油漆刮了
I may have scratched the paint on your bike.
哦   我的
Oh, my...
别逗我笑
Don't make me laugh.
抱歉
Sorry.
去叫其他人 我会找到出路的
Go get the others. I'll find a way out.
你没事吧？
You okay?
哦，我的天
Oh, my God.
雪莉，到我后面去
Sherry, get behind me.
雪莉，快跑
Sherry, run!
克莱尔
Claire!
你这个丑八怪
You ugly fuck!
哦，妈的
Oh, shit!
火箭发射器？
A rocket launcher?
在头等舱找到的
Found it in first class.
我的天
Holy shit.
你们他妈的对这列火车做了什么？
What the fuck you guys do to this train?
生化危机
欢迎来到浣熊市
你终于醒了
You're awake at last.
-我在哪里？      -这不重要
-Where am I?   -That doesn't matter.
等等，我...我不明白
Wait, I... I don't understand.
我以为我死了
I thought I was dead.
是的
You were.
我的眼睛
My eyes.
我的眼睛怎么了？我看不见
What happened to my eyes? I can't see.
这是副作用
It's a side effect.
为了让你复活  我们不得不这样做
One of the things we had to do to bring you back.
还会有其他人的
There will be others.
你还没告诉我你的名字
You never told me your name.
艾达
Ada.
我叫 艾达 - 王
My name is Ada Wong.
你想从我这里得到什么
What do you want from me?